belloflostsouls.net 2019-01-28

# BoLS Privacy Policy - Bell of Lost Souls

BoLS Interactive takes the security of your information seriously.  We do not rent, sell, or share your information with anyone else.  Your information may be stored in systems that we do not own in the course of necessary business. The list below is current as of 05/2018.

Because BELLOFLOSTSOULS.NET gathers certain types of information about our users, we feel you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it.

**COMMITMENT TO YOUR PRIVACY**

This site is owned and operated by BoLS Interactive LLC. Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. We want to make your online experience satisfying and safe.

Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we feel you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it.

**INFORMATION THIS SITE GATHERS AND TRACKS**

BELLOFLOSTSOULS.NET gathers two types of information about users:

Information that users provide through optional, voluntary submissions. These are voluntary submissions to receive our electronic newsletters, to participate in our message boards or forums, to email a friend, and from participation in polls and surveys:

Information BELLOFLOSTSOULS.NET gathers through aggregated tracking information derived mainly by tallying page views throughout our sites. This information allows us to better tailor our content to readers’ needs and to help our advertisers and sponsors better understand the demographics of our audience. Because BELLOFLOSTSOULS.NET derives its revenue mainly from sponsorships, advertisement and / or donations, providing such aggregated demographic data is essential to keeping our service free to users. Under no circumstances does BELLOFLOSTSOULS.NET divulge any information about an individual user to a third party.

BELLOFLOSTSOULS.NET Gathers User Information In The Following Processes:

**Optional Voluntary Information**

We offer the following free services, which require some type of voluntary submission of personal information by users:

**1\. Electronic newsletters (Dispatches)**

We will offer a free electronic newsletter to users. BELLOFLOSTSOULS.NET gathers the email addresses of users who voluntarily subscribe. Users may remove themselves from this mailing list by following the link provided in every newsletter that points users to the subscription management page. Users can also subscribe to the newsletters at the time of registration.

**2\. Message boards/forums**

Users of the site’s Message Boards and Forums must register separately for these services (both are free of charge) in order to post messages, although they needn’t register to visit the site. During registration the user is required to supply a username, password, and email address.

**3\. “E-mail this to a friend” Service**

Our site users can choose to electronically forward a link, page, or documents to someone else by clicking “e-mail this to a friend”. The user must provide their email address, as well as that of the recipient. This information is used only in the case of transmission errors and, of course, to let the recipient know who sent the email. The information is not used for any other purpose.

**4\. Polling**

We may offer interactive polls to users so they can easily share their opinions with other users and see what our audience thinks about important issues. Opinions or other responses to polls are aggregated and are not identifiable to any particular user. BELLOFLOSTSOULS.NET may use a system to “tag” users after they have voted, so they can vote only once on a particular question. This tag is not correlated with information about individual users.

**5\. Surveys**

BELLOFLOSTSOULS.NET may occasionally conduct user surveys to better target our content to our audience. We sometimes share the aggregated demographic information in these surveys with our sponsors, advertisers and partners. We never share any of this information about specific individuals with any third party.

**Children**

Consistent with the Federal Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without requesting parental consent.

**Usage tracking**

BELLOFLOSTSOULS.NET tracks user traffic patterns throughout all of our sites. However, we do not correlate this information with data about individual users. BELLOFLOSTSOULS.NET does break down overall usage statistics according to a user’s domain name, browser type, and MIME type by reading this information from the browser string (information contained in every user’s browser).

BELLOFLOSTSOULS.NET sometimes tracks and catalogs the search terms that users enter in our Search function, but this tracking is never associated with individual users. We use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don’t like based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you.

**COOKIES**

**What are cookies?**

  * Cookies are small data files that are placed on your computer or mobile device when you visit a website. Cookies are widely used by online service providers in order to (for example) make their websites or services work, or to work more efficiently, as well as to provide reporting information.
  * Cookies set by the website owner or service provider (in this case, BoLS Interactive) are called “first party cookies”. Cookies set by parties other than the website owner are called “third party cookies”. Third party cookies enable third party features or functionality to be provided on or through the website or service you are using (such as advertising, interactive content and analytics). The third parties that set these third party cookies can recognize your computer both when it visits the website or service in question and also when it visits certain other websites or services.

**Third Party Cookies**

We also have some opt-in cookies, which require your consent using a pop-up banner at the top of belloflostsouls.net when you first come to visit

  * We use Google Analytics, which means that cookies are used to collect non-identifying information. This is transmitted to servers in the United States owned by Google.
  * We use Quantcast, which means that cookies are used to collect non-identifying information. This is transmitted to servers in the United States owned by Quantcast.
  * We use cookies, in partnership with Google, Rubicon, SOVRN, District M and Division D. These third parties use cookies, web beacons, pixel tags and similar tracking technologies to collect and use certain information about your online activities, either on our Websites and/or other sites or mobile apps, to infer your interests and deliver you targeted advertisements that are more tailored to you based on your browsing activities and inferred interests (“Interest Based Advertising”). For more information about this practice, click here: <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>.  The information collected by these third parties does not include personal information that enables you to be specifically identified (e.g. by reference to your name or email address).

**USE OF INFORMATION**

BELLOFLOSTSOULS.NET uses any information voluntarily given by our users to enhance their experience in our network of sites, whether to provide interactive or personalized elements on the sites or to better prepare future content based on the interests of our users.

As stated above, we use information that users voluntarily provide in order to send out electronic newsletters and to enable users to participate in polls, surveys, message boards, and forums. We send out newsletters to subscribers on a regular schedule (depending on the newsletter), and occasionally send out special editions when we think subscribers might be particularly interested in something we are doing. BELLOFLOSTSOULS.NET never shares newsletter mailing lists with any third parties, including advertisers, sponsors or partners.

When we use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don’t like based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you. We track search terms entered in Search function as one of many measures of what interests our users. But we don’t track which terms a particular user enters.

**SHARING OF THE INFORMATION**

BELLOFLOSTSOULS.NET uses the above-described information to tailor our content to suit your needs and help our advertisers better understand our audience’s demographics. This is essential to keeping our service free. We will not share information about individual users with any third party, except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public.

**SECURITY**

BELLOFLOSTSOULS.NET operates secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection systems. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary and only authorized individuals have access to the information provided by our customers.

**OPT-OUT POLICY**

We give users options wherever necessary and practical. Such choices include:

Opting not to register to receive our electronic newsletters.

Opting not to participate in certain interactive areas, which completely alleviates the need to gather any personally identifiable information from our users

**YOUR CONSENT**

By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by BELLOFLOSTSOULS.NET. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

We collect the following information:

  * Click-stream data
  * HTTP protocol elements
  * Search terms
  * User’s Name
  * Computer information

At the user’s option, we may also collect the following data:

  * Birth Date
  * Email Address
  * Address

This data will be used for the following purposes:

  * Completion and support of the current activity.
  * Web site and system administration.
  * Research and development.

This data will be used by ourselves and our agents.

The following explanation is provided for why this data is collected:

Data collected from all Web users: access logs, and search strings (if entered).

At the user’s option, we will collect the following data:

  * HTTP cookies

This data will be used for the following purposes:

  * Research and development.
  * One-time tailoring.

This data will be used by ourselves and our agents.

**ADDITIONAL INFORMATION**

If you have any other questions about information not covered here, or wish to get in touch about any data-related issues, please contact our data protection officer at _contact@bolsinteractive.com_ or you may contact us by mail at the following address:

BoLS Interactive LLC 1500 Villanova Dr. AUSTIN TX, 78757
